<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<vroom-config xmlns="http://www.openkoncept.net/schema/vroom-config-2.1.xsd"
              xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
              xsi:schemaLocation="http://www.openkoncept.net/schema/vroom-config-2.1.xsd vroom-config-2.1.xsd">
    <webpage uri="/|[/a-zA-Z0-9-_]*.(jsp|html)">
        <stylesheet>
            body, h1, h2, h3, h4, h5, h6 {
            font-family: Sans-serif;
            }
        </stylesheet>
        <event type="onload">
            <call type="update" name="document" attribute="title" value="Vroom 2.1.4"/>
            <call type="update" tag="body" attribute="innerHTML">
<![CDATA[
<h2>Vroom 2.1.4</h2>
<p>
    Vroom is a web application development framework for Java Platform. It's a great mix of MVC and Ajax-enabled
    Event Driven Architecture. Vroom is design using J2EE 1.4 specifications. Applications developed using Vroom
    can run on any J2EE 1.4 compliant web/application server.
</p>
<p>
    With Vroom you can:
</p>
<ul>
    <li>Inject meta tags, stylesheets and scripts</li>
    <li>Control the webpage behaviour without modifying the webpage code</li>
    <li>Bind webpages with server side java beans like Struts Action Forms</li>
    <li>Bind html events with server side java methods like Struts Actions</li>
    <li>Control webpage navigation based on outcome like JSF Navigation</li>
    <li>Access server side variables in Java Script and HTML including request and session objects</li>
</ul>
<p>
    The beauty of this framework is that it's quite simple to use because it doesn't introduce any new API and
    no custom tags required since everything is controlled through an xml-based configuration file. Any
    HTML/XHTML compliant webpage can be managed using Vroom. It provides
    flexibility to bind multiple webpages with one java bean or one webpage with multiple java beans. Binding
    can be defined at multiple levels such as webpage event binding, form event binding, element event binding.
</p>
<p>
    To learn more about the framework, visit the project blog at
    <a href="http://vroom-framework.blogspot.com">vroom-framework.blogspot.com</a>
    or project website at
    <a href="http://www.sourceforge.net/projects/vroom/">www.sourceforge.net/projects/vroom</a>.
</p>
]]>
            </call>
        </event>
        <event type="onload" method="helloWorld" bean-class="net.openkoncept.vroom.VroomTest" var="vt" scope="request">
            <call type="script">
<![CDATA[
alert("#{value}");
]]>
            </call>
        </event>
    </webpage>
</vroom-config>